<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Gallery</string>
    <string name="no_media_found">No media found!</string>
    <string name="refresh">Refresh</string>
    <string name="please_wait">Please wait…</string>
    <string name="sort_by">Sort by</string>
    <string name="date">Date</string>
    <string name="size">Size</string>
    <string name="ascending">Ascending</string>
    <string name="descending">Descending</string>
    <string name="use_as">Use as</string>
    <string name="details">Details</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="all_rights_reserved">All rights reserved.</string>
    <string name="illustrations_credit">Illustrations by Storyset</string>
    <string name="made_by_msartore">Made by msartore</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="third_party_licenses">Third party license</string>
    <string name="more_about_me">More about me</string>
    <string name="license">License</string>
    <string name="glide_title" translatable="false">Glide (image loading and caching)</string>
    <string name="glide_description" translatable="false">Copyright 2014 Google, Inc. All rights reserved.\n\nRedistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:\n\n1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.\n\n2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.\n\nTHIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY GOOGLE, INC. ``AS IS\'\' AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL GOOGLE, INC. OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.</string>
    <string name="kotlin_title" translatable="false">Kotlin (programming language)</string>
    <string name="kotlin_descriptionTitle" translatable="false">Copyright 2010–2020 JetBrains s.r.o. and Kotlin Programming Language contributors.</string>
    <string name="apache_license" translatable="false">"\n\nLicensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the \"License\"); you may not use this file except in compliance with the License. You may obtain a copy of the License at\n\nhttp://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0\n\nUnless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed under the License is distributed on an \"AS IS\" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations under the License."</string>
    <string name="exoplayer_title" translatable="false">Exoplayer (video player)</string>
    <string name="exoplayer_descriptionTitle" translatable="false">Copyright 2014 Google, Inc. All rights reserved.</string>
    <string name="accompanist_title" translatable="false">Accompanist (permission, system ui controller and appcompact theme adapter)</string>
    <string name="accompanist_descriptionTitle" translatable="false">"Copyright 2020 The Android Open Source Project "</string>
    <string name="gallery_description" translatable="false">Copyright © 2022 Massimiliano Sartore\n\nThis program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later version.\n\nThis program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU General Public License for more details.\n\nYou should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License along with this program. If not, see https://www.gnu.org/licenses/</string>
    <string name="permission_request">Permission request</string>
    <string name="permission_request_text">This app has to access your Photo and Media to work. Please grant the permission.</string>
    <string name="permission_rejected">Permission rejected</string>
    <string name="permission_rejected_text">File and Media permission denied. Please, grant us access to the Settings screen.</string>
    <string name="open_settings">Open settings</string>
    <string name="confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="contribute_to_the_project">Contribute to the project</string>
    <string name="donate_to_support_the_project">Donate to support the project</string>
    <string name="convert_to_pdf">Convert to PDF</string>
    <string name="finishing_document">Finishing document…</string>
    <string name="done">Done!</string>
</resources>